Hello everyone welcome back to my channel The
Smart Investor so guys what is here
related to ICI company means ICI Loam Bud General Insurance Company, what is it
exactly on 20th December,
a news had come out here due to
which see the market
was down but this stock was up by 0.20 because of the
news, what is the news that has come out here, let
me show you,
in the news it was what the company has done up to here,
if you go to see here, then if you
scroll down the side, then
exactly what is mentioned here,
which is what is there in it, the company has acquired an
acquisition of 0.04 billion,
which is its percentage
of 0.05, so Mahindra &
is in Mumbai, Maharashtra only and
in which things is it present, which is
exactly what has been mentioned here,
so
you are getting a discount rate also, so if
possible then definitely you should invest in it
So this was the latest news of the company
and I think your doubts have been cleared,
so please like and share this and also do
not forget to subscribe to the channel, thank
you.